https://www.mperkins.co.uk/privacy-notice/

Privacy Notice
Your information
M Perkins & Son Ltd collects some basic information when you contact us either to make enquiry, request prices, samples or place an order for our products.        We collect information about you to process your order, provide service and manage your account.
We maintain a record of each customer containing all previous orders and enquiries. We will hold this information for as long as you are a customer and for a period of time after that.  We will not hold it longer than we consider necessary. This enables us to personalise our service to you and maintain sufficient stock levels and product consistency. We do not use this information for marketing purposes or sharing with third parties with the exception of the limited information we must share with our shippers (in order to dispatch orders), and accounts software provider to process orders.
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at our company address (see below). We may make a small charge for this service. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate at any time.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on the web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 1st May 2018.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any question s about our privacy policy or information we hold about you: by emailing admin@mperkins.co.uk, telephone 01420 541171, or writing to M Perkins & Son Ltd, 2 Weyside Park, Newman Lane, Alton, Hants, GU34 2YY
